Guide to the Lionel W. McKenzie Papers, 1942-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research and Writings Series, 1946-1999 and undated, (12 boxes)
  - Notes, undated, (4 folders) (Box 38)
  - Notes from Harvard, circa 1980 (Box 38)
  - Notes from Madison and Illinois, 1976 (Box 38)
  - Notes from New Haven: Cowles Foundation, 1956 (Box 38)
  - Notes on Anour and Hahn, undated (Box 38)
  - Notes on dual turnpikes, undated (Box 38)
  - Notes on econometrics, 1950s (Box 38)
  - Notes on growth theorem, 1960s (Box 39)
  - Notes on optimal growth, undated (Box 39)
  - Notes on rational choice, undated (Box 39)
  - Notes on taxation from SSRC workshop, 1957 (Box 39)
  - Notes on turnpike theorem, 1960s (Box 39)
  - Notes on turnpikes, undated (Box 39)
  - "Optimal Economic Growth, Turnpike Theorem, and Competitive Dynamics," 1986, (folders 1-6 of 9) (Box 39)
  - "Optimal Economic Growth, Turnpike Theorem, and Competitive Dynamics," 1986, (folders 7-9 of 9) (Box 40)
  - Oxford lectures, circa 1947, circa 1955 (Box 40)
  - Oxford thesis, 1948 (Box 40)
  - Papers, 1950s-1990s, (folders 1-3 of 14) (Box 40)
  - Papers, 1950s-1990s, (folders 4-14 of 14) (Box 41)
  - Presidential lecture, 1979 (Box 41)
  - "Price-Quantity Duality and Turnpike Theorem," 1961 (Box 41)
  - "A Primal Route to the Turnpike and Liapounov Stability," 1982, (folders 1-2 of 4) (Box 41)
  - "A Primal Route to the Turnpike and Liapounov Stability," 1982, (folders 3-4 of 4) (Box 42)
  - Programming of independent sources, 1950-1951 (Box 42)
  - Princeton thesis, 1956 (Box 42)
  - Referee reports, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Research for Warsaw paper, 1970s (Box 42)
  - Review of Collard, etc., 1957, 1984 (Box 42)
  - "A Scholar's Progress," 1999 (Box 42)
  - Social Sciences Encyclopedia, 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Some revised manuscripts, 1980s (Box 42)
  - "Specialization and Efficiency in World Production," 1954 (Box 42)
  - "Stability of Equilibrium and the Value of Positive Excess Demand," 1960 (Box 42)
  - "Theorem and Counter-Example," Swann and Koupeman correspondence, 1960s (Box 42)
  - "Theory of International Trade II," 1966 (Box 42)
  - "Three Turnpike Theorems for a Generalized Leontief Model," 1962 (Box 42)
  - Trade, 1960s (Box 43)
  - "Turnpike Theory," 1976, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - "Turnpike Theory: Some Corrections," 1980 (Box 43)
  - "Turnpike Theory, Discounted Utility, and the Von Neumann Facet," 1983, (5 folders) (Box 43)
  - "Turnpike Theorem of Morishima," 1963 (Box 43)
  - "Turnpike Theorems with Technology and Welfare Function Variable," 1972 (Box 43)
  - "Turnpikes," 1998, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Two reprints, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - "Why Compute Competitive Equilibrium," 1976 (Box 44)
  - Writings by Others, 1949-1959
    - Various authors. "Lectures on the Theory of Games," 1952 (Box 44)
    - Various authors. "Seminar on Convex Sets," 1949-1950 (Box 44)
    - Fan, Ky. "Convex Sets and Their Applications," 1959 (Box 44)
    - Fenchel, W. "Convex Cones, Sets, and Function," 1953 (Box 44)
    - MacLane, Saunders. "Algebraic Topology," 1951 (Box 44)
    - Savage. "Exercises in Math Stat," circa 1951 (Box 44)
    - Tucker, A. W. "Game Theory and Programming," 1955 (Box 44)